<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Swami Venkatesh</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/"/>
 <updated>2018-10-02T07:52:29-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <author>
   <name>Swami Venkatesh</name>
   <email>vswami101@yahoo.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>How to mine a crowd..</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/01/how-to-mine-a-crowd/"/>
   <updated>2018-10-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2018/10/01/how-to-mine-a-crowd</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;takaways-from-exploratory-data-analysis-using-nyc-mta-turnstile-data&quot;&gt;Takaways from Exploratory Data Analysis using NYC MTA Turnstile data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/pexels-photo-1112107.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;NYC crowds&quot; /&gt;
Photo by Jamie McInall from Pexels&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Week one of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thisismetis.com/data-science-bootcamps&quot;&gt;Metis Data Science Bootcamp&lt;/a&gt; saw us wade neck deep into analyzing data - in its full glory, and I kid you not - it was messy! But the final outcome was something, which as a rank newcomer - I was proud of!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project was designed such that we would face the rigors of understanding the data, clean it and analyze it to come up with recommendations for a fictional client. Women Yes Women Tech (WYWT) International wanted us to analyze the &lt;a href=&quot;http://web.mta.info/developers/turnstile.html&quot;&gt;MTA Turnstile data&lt;/a&gt; to suggest where to place their street team of volunteers to maximize sign-ups for their cause and increase attendance in their summer gala.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, why MTA turnstile data, you may ask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;nyc-mta-turnstile-data&quot;&gt;NYC MTA turnstile data&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In 2016, average weekday subway ridership was 5.7 million, the highest since 1948. Annual ridership was 1.757 billion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://web.mta.info/nyct/facts/ffsubway.htm&quot;&gt;MTA info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given this ridership, it should come as no surprise that the data from the turnstiles - that register the traffic through the New York subway system at each entrance of each station every four hours - would be ideal for our analysis. Given the rather &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.surveygizmo.com/resources/blog/survey-response-rates/&quot;&gt;low response rates (10-12%) for external surveys&lt;/a&gt;, identifying stations with the highest footfalls could yield a good conversion rate, i.e, more donors to WYWT’s cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given that WYWT would hold their gala in summer, we pulled out the turnstile data for the months preceding it, from March to May and used it for our analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on our cleaned-up data (maybe I should go over how we did all that in another blog post?), we came up with a list of top stations with the highest footfalls. We focussed on the number of exits from any given station, as we inferred that people would be more amenable to chatting with volunteers at their destination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/stations_by_exits.png&quot; alt=&quot;top stations&quot; /&gt;
Top MTA stations based on the turnstile Data&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-income-angle&quot;&gt;The income angle&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/Exit_map.png&quot; alt=&quot;distribution&quot; /&gt;
GPS locations of the top MTA stations that we selected. Larger circles indicate more foot falls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WYWT is looking to expand on its donor base through the street campaign, so we decided to add income data from Kaggle (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kaggle.com/goldenoakresearch/us-household-income-stats-geo-locations&quot;&gt;household income data&lt;/a&gt;), to supplement the footfall data and get more meaning into our analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We identified the zipcodes around our top stations and mapped the income distribution around these locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/Income_map.png&quot; alt=&quot;income distribution&quot; /&gt;
GPS locations of the income distribution. Darker circles indicate higher incomes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also devised a simple algorithm that mapped both footfall and income data into a single function, adding weights to each component so that we could tweak the recommendations towards either income heavy stations or footfall heavy stations, based on the client’s preference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/Rank_Map.png&quot; alt=&quot;income and footfall&quot; /&gt;
GPS map of top ranked MTA Stations based on the combined income and turnstile data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;our-recommendations&quot;&gt;Our recommendations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;List of top fifty stations based on our combined income and footfall ranking system.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Mondays and Fridays are the best days for positioning street teams at the exits of the stations to maximize their impact as the ridership peaks on those days.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/exits_week.png&quot; alt=&quot;Exits and the day of the week&quot; /&gt;
The turnstile data was separated by the days of the week and aggregated over the entire period of 13 weeks to give rise to the distribution of exits over the days of the week for selected stations with the shadow being the 95% confidence interval around each line plot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: Wednesday traffic seem to be fluctuating more than any other day for the period we analyzed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;next-steps&quot;&gt;Next Steps&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Off to week two and web scraping! Keep an eye on this blog for more updates in the coming weeks! I leave you with some interesting quotes on data from some truly learned people!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;interesting-quotes-on-data&quot;&gt;Interesting Quotes on Data&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“It is a capital mistake to theorize before one has data.”- Arthur Conan Doyle, Author of Sherlock Holmes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Torture the data, and it will confess to anything.” – Ronald Coase, winner of the Nobel Prize in Economics&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The world is one big data problem.”- Andrew McAfee, MIT scientist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Artificially Reimagining Healthcare</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/01/health-and-AI/"/>
   <updated>2018-10-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2018/10/01/health-and-AI</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-personal-journey-towards-data-science&quot;&gt;My personal journey towards Data Science.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Molecular Biologist and Biochemistry PhD by training, I have over a decade of research experience under my belt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, classical molecular biology has, in recent years, evolved technologically, to generate terabytes of digitized data – resulting from genomics and proteomics experiments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About five years ago, I diversified from my core field into genomics and proteomics, which necessarily involved data analysis. I began learning the R language and using it to analyze data sets. My foray into data analysis led to my appreciation of the appeal and power of using R not just to operate on datasets popularly termed as ‘big data’, but to also extract meaningful, statistically-significant analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I published my research results in the journal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/nature11326&quot;&gt;Nature&lt;/a&gt;, and followed it up with another publication in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms13610&quot;&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/a&gt;. These experiences got me interested in learning how to harness the power of data analysis, particularly with the advent of AI techniques in understanding biological data.  And this is just data academic research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, the healthcare industry offers a treasure trove of data in the form of patient database - measurements, images and diagnostic tests - that could amount to 80MB data per person each year. Add to it, fitness data from iPhones and fitbits, government websites (CDC and FDA), insurance claims and other health records – that is a mind-boggling amount of data to sift through, analyze and make sense of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert estimates peg the &lt;a href=&quot;http://fortune.com/2018/03/19/big-data-digital-health-tech/&quot;&gt;health data analytics industry to touch $24 billion by the year 2020&lt;/a&gt;. And with good reason – such investments in the health care industry will decrease healthcare costs for the patient and improve overall well-being of the population as well! Besides, this will bode well for businesses too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is evident from literature survey that supervised and unsupervised machine learning are widely popular and being applied to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-018-03358-3&quot;&gt;categorize the vast plethora of viruses&lt;/a&gt; and in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/09/180917111642.htm&quot;&gt;grading tumors based on their molecular signatures&lt;/a&gt;. But this is just the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This data-driven transformation is not restricted to biology or the health care industry alone. The broad scope of inquiry using data – particularly continuous streams using IOT – will place data analysis as a sought-after skill set.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Introducing Hyde</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2013/12/28/introducing-hyde/"/>
   <updated>2013-12-28T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2013/12/28/introducing-hyde</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hyde is a brazen two-column &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; theme that pairs a prominent sidebar with uncomplicated content. It’s based on &lt;a href=&quot;http://getpoole.com&quot;&gt;Poole&lt;/a&gt;, the Jekyll butler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;built-on-poole&quot;&gt;Built on Poole&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poole is the Jekyll Butler, serving as an upstanding and effective foundation for Jekyll themes by &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/mdo&quot;&gt;@mdo&lt;/a&gt;. Poole, and every theme built on it (like Hyde here) includes the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Complete Jekyll setup included (layouts, config, &lt;a href=&quot;/404&quot;&gt;404&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;/atom.xml&quot;&gt;RSS feed&lt;/a&gt;, posts, and &lt;a href=&quot;/about&quot;&gt;example page&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobile friendly design and development&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Easily scalable text and component sizing with &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;rem&lt;/code&gt; units in the CSS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Support for a wide gamut of HTML elements&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Related posts (time-based, because Jekyll) below each post&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Syntax highlighting, courtesy Pygments (the Python-based code snippet highlighter)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;hyde-features&quot;&gt;Hyde features&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the features of Poole, Hyde adds the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sidebar includes support for textual modules and a dynamically generated navigation with active link support&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Two orientations for content and sidebar, default (left sidebar) and &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/lanyon#reverse-layout&quot;&gt;reverse&lt;/a&gt; (right sidebar), available via &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;body&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; classes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/hyde#themes&quot;&gt;Eight optional color schemes&lt;/a&gt;, available via &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;body&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; classes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/hyde#readme&quot;&gt;Head to the readme&lt;/a&gt; to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;browser-support&quot;&gt;Browser support&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hyde is by preference a forward-thinking project. In addition to the latest versions of Chrome, Safari (mobile and desktop), and Firefox, it is only compatible with Internet Explorer 9 and above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;download&quot;&gt;Download&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hyde is developed on and hosted with GitHub. Head to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/hyde&quot;&gt;GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt; for downloads, bug reports, and features requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Example content</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2012/02/07/example-content/"/>
   <updated>2012-02-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2012/02/07/example-content</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;message&quot;&gt;
  Howdy! This is an example blog post that shows several types of HTML content supported in this theme.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;dis parturient montes&lt;/a&gt;, nascetur ridiculus mus. &lt;em&gt;Aenean eu leo quam.&lt;/em&gt; Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum. Sed posuere consectetur est at lobortis. Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo. Nullam id dolor id nibh ultricies vehicula ut id elit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Etiam porta &lt;strong&gt;sem malesuada magna&lt;/strong&gt; mollis euismod. Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum. Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;inline-html-elements&quot;&gt;Inline HTML elements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTML defines a long list of available inline tags, a complete list of which can be found on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTML/Element&quot;&gt;Mozilla Developer Network&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To bold text&lt;/strong&gt;, use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;To italicize text&lt;/em&gt;, use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Abbreviations, like &lt;abbr title=&quot;HyperText Markup Langage&quot;&gt;HTML&lt;/abbr&gt; should use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;abbr&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;, with an optional &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;title&lt;/code&gt; attribute for the full phrase.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Citations, like &lt;cite&gt;— Mark otto&lt;/cite&gt;, should use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;cite&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;Deleted&lt;/del&gt; text should use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;del&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;ins&gt;inserted&lt;/ins&gt; text should use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;ins&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Superscript &lt;sup&gt;text&lt;/sup&gt; uses &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and subscript &lt;sub&gt;text&lt;/sub&gt; uses &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;sub&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of these elements are styled by browsers with few modifications on our part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;heading&quot;&gt;Heading&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;code&quot;&gt;Code&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;code element&lt;/code&gt; montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-js&quot; data-lang=&quot;js&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Example can be run directly in your JavaScript console
&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Create a function that takes two arguments and returns the sum of those arguments
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;kd&quot;&gt;var&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;adder&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;Function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;a&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;b&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;return a + b&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// Call the function
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;adder&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;// &amp;gt; 8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur. Etiam porta sem malesuada magna mollis euismod. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;gists-via-github-pages&quot;&gt;Gists via GitHub Pages&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo. Donec sed odio dui.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script src=&quot;https://gist.github.com/5555251.js?file=gist.md&quot;&gt; &lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aenean eu leo quam. Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Donec sed odio dui. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lists&quot;&gt;Lists&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur. Etiam porta sem malesuada magna mollis euismod. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Praesent commodo cursus magna, vel scelerisque nisl consectetur et.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Donec id elit non mi porta gravida at eget metus.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Donec ullamcorper nulla non metus auctor fringilla. Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Maecenas sed diam eget risus varius blandit sit amet non magna.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cras mattis consectetur purus sit amet fermentum. Sed posuere consectetur est at lobortis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
  &lt;dt&gt;HyperText Markup Language (HTML)&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;The language used to describe and define the content of a Web page&lt;/dd&gt;

  &lt;dt&gt;Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;Used to describe the appearance of Web content&lt;/dd&gt;

  &lt;dt&gt;JavaScript (JS)&lt;/dt&gt;
  &lt;dd&gt;The programming language used to build advanced Web sites and applications&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Integer posuere erat a ante venenatis dapibus posuere velit aliquet. Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;images&quot;&gt;Images&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quisque consequat sapien eget quam rhoncus, sit amet laoreet diam tempus. Aliquam aliquam metus erat, a pulvinar turpis suscipit at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/800x400&quot; alt=&quot;placeholder&quot; title=&quot;Large example image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/400x200&quot; alt=&quot;placeholder&quot; title=&quot;Medium example image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/200x200&quot; alt=&quot;placeholder&quot; title=&quot;Small example image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tables&quot;&gt;Tables&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aenean lacinia bibendum nulla sed consectetur. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Upvotes&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Downvotes&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tfoot&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Totals&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;21&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;23&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tfoot&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Alice&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;11&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Bob&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Charlie&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nullam id dolor id nibh ultricies vehicula ut id elit. Sed posuere consectetur est at lobortis. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to see something else added? &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/poole/poole/issues/new&quot;&gt;Open an issue.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>What's Jekyll?</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2012/02/06/whats-jekyll/"/>
   <updated>2012-02-06T00:00:00-06:00</updated>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2012/02/06/whats-jekyll</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is a static site generator, an open-source tool for creating simple yet powerful websites of all shapes and sizes. From &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll/blob/master/README.markdown&quot;&gt;the project’s readme&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Jekyll is a simple, blog aware, static site generator. It takes a template directory […] and spits out a complete, static website suitable for serving with Apache or your favorite web server. This is also the engine behind GitHub Pages, which you can use to host your project’s page or blog right here from GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s an immensely useful tool and one we encourage you to use here with Hyde.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find out more by &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll&quot;&gt;visiting the project on GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
